# AKSHAY NAMDEV KADAM

(+91) 7507704246

akshaykadam771@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/akshay-kadam-91543614a/

https://github.com/akshaykadam771

# **PROFILE**

A passionate data science enthusiast having knowledge in Deep Learning, Machine Learning algorithms to solve challenging business problems. Strong background in Python and knowledge of various types of machine learning algorithms and Deep Learning algorithms. Hands on experience of creating projects using Machine Learning and Deep Learning.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### DATA SCIENCE INTERN

#### Ineuron.ai ( Aug 2020 - Present )

#### **Project:- Human Activity recognition Using Pose Estimation**

- Detect various human activities such as :-
- Fight Detection, Attack Detection, Jump Detection etc
- Using Pose Estimation models.

#### ELECTRONICS R&D INTERN

#### Bramhansh Technology Pvt ltd. (Oct 2019 - Jan 2020)

#### **Project:- Bone Conduction Headphones**

 Bone conduction headphones work by vibrating against the bones in your cheek or upper jaw, which in turn sends those vibrations to the inner ear, bypassing the ear canal completely. Since they don't depend on the eardrum, they can be great for people with hearing deficiencies, and since they aren't in or over your ear, you'll be able to hear what's happening around you.

## **CERTIFICATES**

- " Machine learning Master's " from Ineuron.ai (SEP 2020)
- "Python for Data Science "from Ineuron.ai (MAY 2020)
- Data Science Architecture from Ineuron.ai (MAY 2020)
- " Machine learning " Course from Coursera. ( Jan 2020 )
- " Machine learning " Course from Udemy. (Feb 2020)

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

• Programming Language:- Python, Embedded C

• Tool / IDE :- Pycharm, Jupyter Notebook, Proteus, Keil

• Operating system :- Linux(Ubuntu), Windows

• Cloud Platform :- Heroku , Pivotal

Databases :- MongoDBWeb-Framework :- Flask

• **Electronics** :- Embedded System, Microcontroller, IOT

### **PROJECTS**

### Satellite-Image-Object-Detection

Language:- Python | Algorithm:- Mask-Rcnn | framework:- Flask

- It is 'Mask-Rcnn' & 'Flask' based "Satellite-Image-Object-Detection" project.
- Purpose of this project is to make a model which can detect various objects (River, Forest, Building, etc.) present in the satellite image.
- This model will detect the objects present in the Satellite image as well as for accurate positioning it will Segment the detected objects using "Semantic Segmentation".

Github-Link :- https://github.com/akshaykadam771/SATELLITE-IMAGE-OBJECTS-RECOGNITION

LinkedIn-Link :- https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:6708357131101462528/

### Vehicle Number Plate Detection

Language :- Python | Algorithm :- TFOD & EasyOcr | framework :- Flask

- "Vehicle Number Plate Detection" using Tensorflow Object Detection using "SSD" algorithm and Flask Framework.
- Purpose of this project is to detect the number plate from vehicle and give the information about the vehicle.
- The model will Detect the number plate and using "SSD" TFOD model and after detecting it it will convert it into text using "EasyOcr" method.
- Finally it will give the information about the Vehicle Number and its State.

Github-Link :- https://github.com/akshaykadam771/VEHICLE-NUMBER-PLATE-DETECTION

LinkedIn-Link: - https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:6704622376937771008/

# Wine Quality Prediction

Language:- Python | Algorithm:- Decision-Tree | framework:- Flask

- "Wine Quality Prediction" web application using "Decision-Tree" Machine Learning algorithm & using "Flask" framework which is deployed on "Heroku" cloud platform.
- In this App, we can predict the quality of red wine. In prediction it gives score between O(very bad) 10(excellent).

Github-Link :- https://github.com/akshaykadam771/Wine-Quality-Prediction

App link :- https://wine-quality-predicton.herokuapp.com/

#### Diabetes Prediction

Language :- Python | Algorithm :- Logistic-Regression | framework :- Flask

- "Diabetes Prediction" web application using "Logistic-Regression" Machine Learning algorithm & using "Flask" framework which is deployed on "Heroku" cloud platform.
- In this App, we can predict weather you have a diabetes or not.

Github-Link :- https://github.com/akshaykadam771/Diabetes-Prediction-

App link :- https://diabetes-predicton.herokuapp.com/

# **EDUCATION**

B.TECH (E&TC)	Government College of Engineering, Karad	8.63 (CGPA)	( 2016 – 2019 )
DIPLOMA (E&TC)	PVPIT, Budhgaon.	91.29 %	( 2014 – 2016 )
H.S.C.	Willingdon college, Sangli	55.23 %	( 2012 – 2014 )
S.S.C.	Sangli high school, Sangli	76.20 %	( 2009 – 2012 )

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Runner up in Mutant at ADCET College of Engineering, Ashta. (2019)".
- 1st rank in Project-Expo Aavishkar 2K18, Government College of Engineering Karad. (2018)"
- 1st rank in Project-Expo Innovation 2K18, SIT College of Engineering. (2018)
- Runner up in Mutant at Walchand College of Engineering, Sangli. (2017 & 2018).
- Participated in "Whirlpool Hackethon 2018".

### PERSONAL DETAILS

Name :- Akshay Namdev Kadam

Date of BirthHarital StatusJuly 1996Unmarried

• Current Address :- Cozy homes Wagholi, Pune, Maharashtra, India.

• Permanent Address: - A/P Bamnoli, Tal-Miraj, Dist-Sangli, Maharashtra, India.

• Language known :- English, Hindi, Marathi.

### **DECLARATIONS**

I, hereby declare that all the information specified in resume is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Date:

Mr. Akshay Namdev Kadam

Place: